{"data":[{"question":"There was so many people in front of me that I couldn't see all the singers on the stage clearly.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was","b":"so many","c":"on","d":"clearly","answer":"1","explain":"- Was-> were","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Give the package to whomever has authority to sign for it.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"whomever","b":"has","c":"to sign","d":"it","answer":"1","explain":"- Whomever-> whoever","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"I have never had a most amusing song book than this one before.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"never","b":"most","c":"amusing","d":"before","answer":"2","explain":"- Most-> more","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"John has visited Hawaii and Alaska, and he assures me that he likes Alaska the best.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has visited","b":"assures","c":"that","d":"the best","answer":"4","explain":"- The best-> the most","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Don't you think this is the most boring song you had ever heard?\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Don't","b":"this is","c":"the most boring","d":"had ever heard","answer":"4","explain":"-Had ever heard-> have ever heard","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"This fridge is very old to keep things at a proper temperature.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"very","b":"to keep","c":"at","d":"temperature","answer":"1","explain":"- Very->too","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"The children were surprised when the teacher made them to close their books.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were surprised","b":"when","c":"made","d":"to close","answer":"4","explain":"- To close-> close","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"We were pleased to have the opportunity to watch such talented dancers to perform a highly new ballet.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were pleased","b":"to watch","c":"such talented","d":"to perform","answer":"4","explain":"- To perform-> perform","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"We believe that she already feels very badly about her mistake.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"already feels","b":"badly","c":"about","d":"mistake","answer":"2","explain":"- Badly-> bad","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"I put the food in the fridge because I wanted him to get cold.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"put","b":"in","c":"him","d":"to get","answer":"3","explain":"Very Good! Correc\n\n- Him-> it","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"}]}